[Intro - Instrumental]
In the beginning there was darkness
And then came the light (the light, the light)
Across the cosmos we're wandering
Through the eternal night (eternal night)
Stars are calling out our names (calling, calling)
Dancing in the void
We are stardust, we are flame (we are flame)
Nothing can be destroyed
[Chorus] Take me to the universe
Where the galaxies collide (collide, collide)
Show me all the wonders first
In this cosmic ride (cosmic ride)
We are infinite and free (infinite)
Floating through space and time
This is our destiny (destiny)
To reach the sublime
[Bridge - Instrumental break]
Beyond the edge of reason (beyond, beyond)
We'll find our way back home
[Final Chorus] Take me to the universe
Where the galaxies collide
[Outro - Fade out]